Inventory of the Mimi Benzell papers, 1897-1972 (bulk 1930-1972)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Legal Papers (All pertain to The Metropolitan Opera Association, Inc., and Mimi Benzell legal matters, unless otherwise noted):
  - Legal Papers, Legal Documents:
    - Memorandum of defendant, Mimi Benzell Gould submitted in opposition to Plaintiff's motion for a temporary injunction, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 7 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Memorandum of defendant, Mimi Benzell, submitted in support of her motion to require plaintiff to serve an amended complaint, seperately stating and numbering its causes of action, etc., Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 23 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Memorandum of defendant, Mimi Benzell Gould, submitted in opposition to Plaintiff's motion for a temporary injunction, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 34 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Bill of Particulars, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., and Endorsements, Inc., defendents, 24 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Notice of Motion, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., and Endorsements, Inc., defendents, 7 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., and Endorsements, Inc., defendents, 5 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Notice of Examination before trial, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 4 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 80 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - At a Special Term, Part III of the Supreme Court of the State of New York, held in and for the County of New York at the Court House thereof, Foley Square, in the Borough of Manhattan, City and State of New York, on the 7th day of January 1957, Hon. Felix C. Benvenga, present, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., and Endorsements, Inc., defendents, 9 pages, 2 letters attached, 01/07/1957 (Box 52)
    - Stipulation of Settlement, Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of New York, Metropolitan Opera Association Inc., Plaintiff, against Mimi Benzell Gould, a/k/a Mimi Benzell, Loft's Candy Shop, Inc., Al Paul Lefton Company, Inc. and Al Paul Lefton Company New York Division, Inc., defendents, 7 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - Agreement between Mimi Benzell and Henry W. Herrman for a cruise on the Empress of Australia sailing April 2, 1938, April 1, 1938, 1 pg, attachment, 04/01/1938-04/02/1938 (Box 52)
  - Legal Papers, Newspaper Clippings:
    - By Mr. Justice Benvenga, Metropolitan Opera Association, Inc., v. Gould, 1 piece, undated (Box 52)
    - New York Post, 1 piece, 02/09/1956 (Box 52)
    - New York Times, 1 piece, 02/13/1956 (Box 52)
    - Variety, 1 piece, 02/08/1956 (Box 52)
  - Legal Papers, Press Releases:
    - "Mimi Benzell and the Metropolitan Opera Reach Agreement", 2 pages, undated (Box 52)
    - William Morris Agency, New York, Billing: Mimi Benzell, 100% Glamourous Star of Opera, Concerts and TV, 50%, 15 pages, undated (Box 52)
  - Legal Papers, Miscellaneous:
    - handwritten letter, by Mimi, 10 pages, pencil, undated (Box 52)
- Motion Pictures (8mm):
  - Nebraska, Texas, Wilbur and Walter; Marton and Walter, Felix (Knight), Virginia, open pit mine; El Paso, quartz, Felix (Knight), Salt Lake, plan to Chicago, 10-11/1947; 1948; 04/1947 (Box 53)
  - Met. Tour to Calif. Leild, L.A., San Francisco; California, Phoenix, Texas, from air, cross country, Essie and sister-in-law; Nate King, 1948 (Box 53)
  - Mimi and Walter, Camp Unity, Jones Beach, Jean and Mimi, Tanglewood; Mimi, Miami, Florida (Marine Land); Mimi, Rio Grande (Felix Knight); Mimi, Mom, Pop Gould, Florida, 1949 (Box 53)
  - Virginia City, Leon and Mimi; Yellowstone Park, Mimi and Leon; Fire Island, Mimi, Walter, Larry and Jackie, undated (Box 53)
  - Boulder Dam, Las Vegas at pool; Halldorado, Walter and Kenny; Jackie Bertell, Vacation - Frankel Farks, Las Vegas, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Lucille, Thomas John; John Westbrook's mother and house; John; Tower of London; Q.M., undated (Box 53)
- Motion Pictures (16mm):
  - "Royal Showcase", Print No. #13, 06/01/1952 (Box 53)
  - "Show Boat", #1, undated (Box 53)
  - Unidentified, 2 reels, one with note attached, undated (Box 53)
- Music Scores:
  - "The Abduction from the Seraglio", Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, English translation by Ruth and Thomas Martin, Boosey and Hawkes, Inc., New York, U.S.A., 175 pages, undated (Box 52)
  - "Album of Cole Porter Songs", Chappell and Company, Inc., New York, 48 pages, undated (Box 52)
  - "Album of Twenty Songs", Gabriel Faure, Volume III, Edward B. Marks Music Corportation, New York, 87 pages, 1945 (Box 52)
  - "Album of Twenty Five Songs", Gabriel Faure, Volume II, Edward B. Marks Music Corportation, New York, 104 pages, 1945 (Box 52)
  - "Allez-Vous-En, Go Away" from "Can-Can", words and music by Cole Porter, Buxton Hill Music Corporation, New York, 50 pages, 1944 (Box 52)
  - "All Star Famous Songs", Broadway Music Corporation, New York, 50 pages, 1944 (Box 52)
  - "America Sings", edited by Hugo Frey, Robbins Music Corporation, 143 pages, 1935 (Box 52)
  - "Anema E Core", English lyrics by Mann Curtis and Harry Akst, Italian lyrics by Tito Manilo, music by Salve d'Esposito, MCA Music, New York, 4 pages, 1950, 1959 (Box 52)
  - "Anthology of Modern French Song", a collection of thirty-nine songs, by French composers, collected and edited by Max Spicker, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 187 pages, 1912 (Box 52)
  - "Ariadne auf Naxos", Ricahrd Strauss, Adolph Burstner, Berlin, Paris, France, 19 pages, 1 copy, French translation, German translation, 1912, 1916 (Box 52)
  - "Arias from Oratorios and Cantatas; My Heart Ever Faithful", Johann Sebastian Bach, first series, Oliver Ditson Company, Philadelphia, Penn, 7 pages, undated (Box 52)
  - "Arie Antiche", da Alessandro Praisotti, Volume Terzo, G. Ricordi and C., Milano, 186 pages, 1952 (Box 52)
  - Arie Antiche, Alessandro Praisotti, Volume Primo, G. Ricordi and C., Milano, Rome, 129 pages, Italian translation, 1947 (Box 52)
  - "Arie Antiche", da Alessandro Praisotti, Volume Secundo, Milano, Rome, 130 pages, Italian translation, 1947 (Box 52)
  - "Around the World", lyrics by Harold Adamson, music by Victor Young, Victor Young Publications, Inc., Beverly Hills, California, 2 pages, 1956 (Box 52)
  - "Arthur Tracy, The Street Singer", 78 pages, undated (Box 52)
  - "Art Songs for School and Studio", edited by Mabelle Glenn and Alfred Spouse, Oliver Ditson Company, Bryn Mawr, Penn., 64 pages, 1930 (Box 52)
  - "Bach, French Suites", Johann Sebastian Bach, Edition Wood, The B. F. Wood Music Co., London, England, 55 pages, undated (Box 54)
  - "Bach, Songs and Airs", Johann Sebastian Bach, Augener's Edition, Book II, Augener Ltd., London, England, 118 pages, undated (Box 54)
  - "Before the Crucifix (Dinanzi al Crocifisso)", sacred song, Frank La Forge, words by Princess Gabrielle Wrede, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1912 (Box 54)
  - "Bergerettes: Twenty Romances and Songs of the Eighteenth Century", collected and harmonized by J.B. Weckerlin, English translations and Sigmund Spaeth, G. Schirmer Inc., New York, 53 pages, undated (Box 54)
  - "Beside Still Waters", sacred song, words and music by Bernard Hamblen, Enoch and songs, New York, 7 pages, 1925 (Box 54)
  - "La Boheme", by G. Puccini, G. Ricordi and Co., New York, 7 pages, 1912 (Box 54)
  - "Boney Gnillen", words and music by Herbert Haufrecht, Bronde Brothers, New York, 38 pages, 1953 (Box 54)
  - "The Book of a Thousand Songs", Actually containing more than a thousand standard songs of every description, arranged for playing or singing, Mimil Publsihing company, Incorporated, New York, 535 pages, 1946 (Box 54)
  - "Bucky, The Bucking Bronco", words and music by Milton Pascal, Gerald Marks, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1950 (Box 54)
  - "Butterfly", Commissioner role, pages 85-88, 128-134, undated (Box 54)
  - "Button Up Your Overcoat", by B. G. DeSylva, Lew Brown and Ray Henderson, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1928 (Box 54)
  - "By The Waters of Babylon", words taken from Psalm CXXXVII, music by Vernon Eville, Boosey and Company, Inc., New York, 6 pages, 1928 (Box 54)
  - "Canciones de Navidad", Banks, Upshaw and Company, Dallas, English and Spanish translation, 27 pages, 2 copies, 1961 (Box 54)
  - "Cansonettas and Songs", Peters Edition, Joseph Haydn, C. F. Peters Corporation, 77 pages, English and German translations, undated (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias: W.A. Variations", selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Series II, Carl and Fischer Inc., New York, 21 pages, 1941 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias", selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Series II, G. Donizetti, "O Could We Lightly Fly", Carl and Fischer Inc., 13 pages, 1942 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias: Ariette from "Zemire and Azor", selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Series II, Carl Fischer, New York, 5 pages, 1942 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias: H. Proch, Theme and Variations", Series II, selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Carl Fischer Inc., New York, 15 pages, 1942 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias", selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Series II, C. Gounod, "Little Swallow", Carl and Fischer Inc., 15 pages, 1942 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias", selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Series II, A.E.M Gretry, "No More Shall Sorrow", Carl Fischer, Inc., 7 pages, 1944 (Box 54)
  - "Celebrated Songs and Arias: L. Delibes, Ballerina", series I, selected and arranged by Frank La Forge, Carl Fischer, Inc., New York, 1946, 7 pages (Box 54)
  - "Charles Gilbert Spross: That's The World In June", The John Church, Cincinnati, New York, and London, 5 pages, 1912 (Box 54)
  - "Chopin", Frederick Chopin, Schirmer's Library, English version by Dr. Theo. Baker, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 51 pages, 1897 (Box 54)
  - "A Christmas Alleluia", words and music by Samuel Richards Gaines, J. Fischer and Bros., New York, 5 pages, 1928 (Box 54)
  - Christmas Carols From Many Countries, by Satis N. Coleman and Elin K. Jorgensen, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 102 pages, 1934 (Box 54)
  - "Christmas Eve", poem by Joyce Kilmer, music by Richard Hageman, Galaxy Music Corporation, New York, 7 pages, 1936 (Box 54)
  - "Christmas, It's Carols, Customs and Legends", compiled and arranged by Ruth Heller, Hall and McCreary Company, Chicago, 112 pages, attachment, undated (Box 54)
  - "Classical Spanish Songs", Obradors, International Music Company, New York City, 27 pages, 1950-1959 (Box 54)
  - "Classical Spanish Songs", Obradors, International Music Company, New York City, 27 pages, 1950-1959 (Box 54)
  - "Classic Italian Songs", edited by Mabelle Gleen andBernard U. Taylor, Oliver Ditson Company, Inc., Chicago, Illinois, 64 pages, 1936 (Box 54)
  - "Collection of Cantatas and Oratorios: Elijah, Mendelssohn", New York, A. W. Tams, 198 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "Collection of Christmas Carols", The Boston Music Co., Octavo Church Music, Boston, Massachussetts, 19 pages, 4 copies, undated (Box 55)
  - "Coloratura Songs", by favorite composers, Series One, G. Schirmer Inc., New York, Gaetano Donizetti, "The Gypsy-Maid, (La Zingara)", 9 pages, 1901 (Box 55)
  - "Coloratura Songs", Series One, by favorite composers, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 15 pages, 1901 (Box 55)
  - "Come Unto Me", sacred song, by Gertrude Cady, Harold Flammer, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1929 (Box 55)
  - "Complete Method for Rhythmical Articulation", Pasquale Bona, English text by Ambrose Davenport (Italian and English text), edition White-Smith, 87 pages, 1905 (Box 55)
  - "Composicoes de Heitor Villa-Lobos: Noite de Luar", Sampaio Araiyo and Cie., Rio de Janeiro, 5 pages, Spanish translation, undated (Box 55)
  - "Composicoes de Heitor Villa-Lobos: Confidencia", Sampaio Araiyo and Cie., Rio de Janeiro, 5 pages, Spanish translation, undated (Box 55)
  - "Composicoes de Heitor Villa-Lobos: Amor and Perfidia", Sampaio Araiyo and Cie., Rio de Janeiro, 3 pages, Spanish translation, undated (Box 55)
  - "Conga-Land Album", Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, New York, 48 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "Contemporary American Songs", Associated Music Publishers, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1948 (Box 55)
  - "The Creation", new translation by Robert Shaw and Alice Parker, Lawson-Gould, Music Publishers, Inc., New York, 154 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "The Creation", music by Joseph Haydn, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 154 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "The Creation", Joseph Haydn, new translation by Robert Shaw and Alice Parker, Lawson-Gould, Music Publishers, Inc., New York, 154 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "Deanna Durbin'a Favorite Songs and Arias" edited by Andres de Seguola, new English lyrics by Ann Ronell, G. Schirmer, New York, 61 pages, 1939 (Box 55)
  - "Der Junge Mozart", Carl Stneber, Brncknerverley Wiesbaden GMBH, 119 pages, undated (Box 55)
  - "Der Solfeges", Solfege, Henry Lemoine and Cie., Paris, France, 78 pages, French translation, 1910, 1913 (Box 55)
  - "Die Vogel", Walter Braundels, 10 pages, 1920 (Box 55)
  - "Doctor Sniffleswiper (A Child's Best Friend)", words and music by Jill Jackson and Sy Miller, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1953 (Box 55)
  - "Douze Secces De Gilbert Becaud", Album No. 2, Editions Raoul Breton, France, 36 pages, 1954 (Box 55)
  - "Early Italian Songs and Airs", Vol. I, Caccini to Bononcini, Oliver Ditson Company, Pennsylvania, 167 pages, 1923 (Box 56)
  - "Early Italian Songs and Airs", Vol. II, Provenzale to Supriani, Oliver Ditson Company, Pennsylvania, 183 pages, 1924 (Box 56)
  - "The Earth Is The Lord's", music by Ward-Stephens, Chappell and Co., Ltd., 8 pages, 1917 (Box 56)
  - "Easter Carol", by Grace Bush, and G. Schiermer, Inc., New York, 5 pages, attachment, 1937 (Box 56)
  - "The Ernesto Lecuona Songs Success Album", Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, New York, 31 pages, undated (Box 56)
  - "Estelle Liebling Arrangements and Editings for Coloratura Voice with Piano: Thomas, Amrose, Je Suis Titania (polomaise from Mignon)", G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 11 pages, 1901 (Box 56)
  - "Estelle Liebling", Series I, Gaetano Donizetti, "Arden Gl'incensi" ("The Mad Scientist"), English version by Henry G. Chapman, Gaetan Donizetti, edited by Estelle Liebling, 11 pages, 1938 (Box 56)
  - "Estelle Liebling Arrangements and Editings for Coloratura Voice with Piano: Heinrich Proch, Theme and Variations", Series I, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 11 and 7 pages, 2 parts, 1940 (Box 56)
  - "Everybody's Favorite Neopolitan Songs", Amsco Music Publishing Company, New York, 192 pages, 1938 (Box 56)
  - "Face The Music", Sam H. Harris presented, lyrics and music by Irving Berlin, Irving Berlin, Inc., New York, 6 pages, 1932 (Box 56)
  - "The Favorite Songs of Miguelito Valdes", Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, Radio City, New York, 48 pages, undated (Box 56)
  - "50 Art Songs From The Modern Repertoire", G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 214 pages, 1939 (Box 56)
  - "Fifty Famous Favorites and Fifty Other Favorites", Robbins Edition, arranged and edited by Hugo Frey, Robbins Music Corporation, New York, 95 pages, 1942 (Box 56)
  - "Fifty One Selected Songs", Hugo Wold, The Joseph Patelson Music House, New York, 167 pages, undated (Box 56)
  - "Fifty Shakespeare Songs", The Musicians Library, Oliver Ditson Company, Pennsylvania, 157 pages, 1906 (Box 56)
  - "Five German Poems: Auf genhermem Waldespgads", Charles T. Griffes, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 5 pages, German and English translation, 1909 (Box 56)
  - "Flanders Requiem", ("America's Answer"), by Frank La Forge, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 7 pages, 1919 (Box 56)
  - "Fling Wide The Gates", sacred solo for Palm Sunday, by Harry Rowe Shelley, Philadelphia Theodore Presser Co., 6 pages, 1924 (Box 56)
  - "La Flora", Volume Terzo, edite da Knud Jeppesen, Wilhelm Hansen Copenhagen, 138 pages, Italian translation, 1949 (Box 56)
  - "Folk Song Arrangements", Benjamin Britten, Volume 2, Boosey and Hawkes, Ltd., Paris, France, 40 pages, 1 copy, undated (Box 56)
  - "40 French Hits of Our Times", enlish and French lyrics, Leeds Music Corporation, New York, 132 pages, 1959 (Box 56)
  - "Four Little Love Songs", for high voice and piano, the verses by Sara Teasdale, the music by Frank St. Leger, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 13 pages, 1917 (Box 56)
  - "Francisco Mignone", edicoces tupy, 18 pages, Spanish translation, undated (Box 56)
  - "Frank Sinatra's Songs of Romance", Remick Music Corporation, New York, 27 pages, 1953 (Box 56)
  - "Funf Sieder! Wiengenlied", Richard Strauss, Adolph Furstner, Berlin, 15 pages, German and English translation, 1899 (Box 56)
  - "G. Verdi", "La Traviata, Addio Del Passato (Farewell No, All Past Pleasures)", Oliver Ditson Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 7 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "G. Verdi", "La Traviata, Ah! Was It He (Ah, fors e lui)", Oliver Ditson Company, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 17 pages, 1907 (Box 57)
  - "Geoffrey O' Hara Songs", Forster Music Publisher Inc., Chicago, Illinois, 6 pages, 1925 (Box 57)
  - "The Gooney-Bird Song", words by Joe Darion, music by George Kleinsinger, M. Witmarks and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1951 (Box 57)
  - "Gotta Get Some Shut-Eye", lyrics by Johnny Mercer, music by Walter Donaldson, 5 pages, 1939 (Box 57)
  - "Guffy The Goofy Gobbler", words and music by Milton Pascal and Gerald Marks, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1950 (Box 57)
  - "Harry Von Tilzer's Old Time Favorite Hits", Harry Von Tilzer Music Pub. Co., New York, 65 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Historietes", H. Villa-Lobos, Rio De Janeiro, Spanish translation, 19 pages, 1920 (Box 57)
  - "Hits of Bygone Days" Should I Be Sweet", Series One, words by B.G. De Sylva, music by Vincent Youmans, Music Publishers Holding Corporation, New York, 7 pages, 1933 (Box 57)
  - "Hymn of the Last Summer", sacred song, Boston: Oliver Ditson Company, 7 pages, 1925 (Box 57)
  - "I'm Glad I'm Not a Rubber Ball", words and music by Ray Charles and Myron Dutton, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1951 (Box 57)
  - "If I Had A Dollar Bill Tree", words and music by Mann Curtis, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 4 pages, 1950 (Box 57)
  - "If I Knew You and You Knew Me", words by Nixon Waterman, music by James G. MacDermid, Forster Music Publisher, Inc., Chicago, Illinois, 6 pages, 1921 (Box 57)
  - "If You Loved Me Truly", from "Can-Can" words and music by Cole Porter, Buxton Hill Music Corporation, 5 pages, 1953 (Box 57)
  - "I Have Dreamed Rodgers and Hammerstein's 'The King and I'", music by Richard Rodgers, book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, based on the novel "Anna and the King of Siam" by Margaret Landon, Williamson Music, Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1951 (Box 57)
  - "I've Told Ev'ry Little Star", from "Music In The Air", book and lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, music by Jerome Kern, T. B. Harms Company, New York, 5 pages, 1932 (Box 57)
  - "I Love You", from "Song of Norway", music by Edward Grieg, musical adaptation and lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest, book by Milton Lazarus from a story by Homer Curran, Chappel and Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1944 (Box 57)
  - "I Love You So", from the musical play, "The Merry Widow", words by Adrian Ross, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1941 (Box 57)
  - "Inflammatus et Accensus" (When Thou Comest), Blue Octavo Series, by Rossini, Harold Flammer Publisher Incorporation, sacred, New York, 11 pages, 1909 (Box 57)
  - "In The Chapel In Moonlight", by Billy Hull, Shapiro Bernstein and Co., Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1936 (Box 57)
  - "In The Judy Garland Manner", by Ann Ronell, G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 56 pages, 1940 (Box 57)
  - "In The Still Of The Night", the Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer Production, "Rosalie", Cole Porter, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 7 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Intimate Song", a collection of gay songs from musical comedies, Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 52 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Intimate Song", Chappell and Co., Inc., New York, 52 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Isn't It Romantic?", words by Lorenz Hart, music by Richard Rodgers, Famous Music Corporation, New York, 5 pages, 1932 (Box 57)
  - "Italianisches Liederbuch", Hugo Wolf, Band I, Lipzig, C. F. Peters, Editions Peter, 35 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Italianisches Liederbuch", Hugo Wolf, Band III, Lipzig, C. F. Peters, Editions Peter, 39 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "It's All Right With Me", from "Can-Can", words and music by Cole Porter, Buxton Hill Music Corporation, 7 pages, 1953 (Box 57)
  - "(It's No) Sin", lyrics by Chester R. Shull, music by George Hoven, Algonquin Music Inc., New York, 4 pages, 1951 (Box 57)
  - "It's Not The Whistle That Pulls The Train", words and music by Dick Manning, M. Witmark and Sons, New York, 5 pages, 1954 (Box 57)
  - "It Might As Well Be Spring", music by Richard Rodgers, lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II, from "State Fair", Williamson Music Inc., New York, 5 pages, 1945 (Box 57)
  - "I Will Light Up Mine Eyes", Psalm 121, Rafael Navarro, The H. W. Gray Company, New York, 5 pages, 1918 (Box 57)
  - "James G. MacDermid", James G. MacDermid, Fine Arts Building, Chicago, Illinois, 1908 (Box 57)
  - "Jeanette MacDonald's Favorite Operatic Airs and Concert Songs", G. Schiermer, Inc., New York, 83 pages, 1940 (Box 57)
  - "Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring from Cantata No. 147", Johann Sebastian Bach, Galaxy Music Corporation, New York, 7 pages, 1947 (Box 57)
  - "Johannes Brahms Songs", Vol. II, Edwin F. Kalmus, Scarsdale, New York, 177 pages, undated (Box 57)
  - "Johannes Brahms Songs With Piano Accompaniment: Wiegenlied (Cradle Song)", G. Schirmer, Inc., New York, 3 pages, 1910 (Box 57)
  - "Joseph Marx Lieder Songs, Chants", English words by John Bernhoff, Universal Edition, A.G., Wien, Leipzig, 7 pages, 1930 (Box 57)
  - "Kanzonetten Und Lieder", Joseph Haydn, Edition Peters, C. F. Peters, Leipzig, 77 pages, English and German translation, undated (Box 57)